Hi, my name is Shevin and I am an administrator at Försäkringskassan.
To receive compensation when you participate in a program at the Employment Service
Do you need to take care of your job seeker and follow it
Plan and the agreements available.
If you misbehave or extend your time in unemployment
May the Employment Service decide that you are losing the right
to compensation for one or more days.
Examples of things that make you risk being without compensation
can be;
that you do not submit activity report in time,
not attending planned meetings and activities without valid reason,
Not reported absence to the Employment Service,
not actively looking for a job, thanks no
for job or education that you have been asked to apply.
If you misbehave repeatedly
Increases the number of days you become without compensation.
First time you get a warning,